mensunderwearstore.com 2012-06-11

# MensUnderwearStore.com Security Statement & Privacy Policy

## Security Statement

### Third Party  
Security Verification

MensUnderwearStore.com uses industry-leading 256-bit encryption technologies when transferring and receiving your information on our site. Our secure certificate is managed by Comodo, a leading security certificate authority. When you are entering personal information, look for either a solid key icon or a locked padlock icon at the lower portion of your browser. This indicates that your site is secured through the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. In browsers that support extended validation (EV), the address bar will also turn green to add another level of verification that this website is secure.

MensUnderwearStore.com has appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have gathered from you or from our site so you can feel comfortable and secure.

MensUnderwearStore.com was certified PCI (Payment Card Industry) Compliant in April, 2008. The PCI Data Security Standard covers security scanning requirements of VISA's Cardholder Information Security Program (CISP), MasterCard's Site Data Protection (SDP) program, American Express' CID security program, and the Discover Card Information Security and Compliance (DISC) program.

PCI Compliance means our servers passed tests that probe all of the known methods hackers use to access private information, in addition to vulnerabilities that would allow malicious software to gain access to or disrupt our network.

The PCI Compliance scan was conducted by ScanAlert, a "Qualified Independent Scan Vendor" accredited by Visa USA, Mastercard International, American Express, Discover Card and JCB to perform network security compliance audtis conforming to the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standards.

If you have any questions regarding this statement, please contact our Internet service department.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

When you visit our Internet e-commerce site, our server automatically collects the following non-personally identifiable information: your Internet service provider's address; and information on the pages you access on our site. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to our site and which areas of the site appear to be most useful, as well as to generate statistical reports.

Our server also collects personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit, such as when you purchase a product or products at our online storefront or enter the sweepstakes. **This information is used by us solely for the purpose for which it was intended and it is not shared with or sold to third parties for any reason.**

MensUnderwearStore.com has appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have gathered from you or from our site so you can feel comfortable and secure.

If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact our Internet service department.
